Swatantra Mishra

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India



linkedin.com/in/swatantra3



swatantramishra1@gmail.com



9538406805

Summary

About 5.7 years of overall experience in complete SDLC of the project from Requirements Analysis, High-Level, Low-Level Design, Build, Unit Testing, Module Testing, Data Analysis, Support and Deployment to the production of various Hybride applications.

A pragmatic team player who thrives on producing tangible results that add real benefit and possess strong analytical and problem-solving skills, inspiring team player with good communication skills and has the potential and confidence to take up complex and challenging project assignments.

Competencies:

- Angular
- React Js
- JavaScript
- HTML, CSS
- Github, BitBucket
- Figma

URL- http://www.swatantra.xyz(wip)

Article - https://medium.com/@swatantramishra1/react-client-side-routing-404-error-72e7d0596766

Experience



Sr Software Engineer

Supr Daily

Feb 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months +)

I am working towards learning which allow me to experiment which impacts millions in small changes so need to have fully control in design and development time.

Proud of on product which i am working on, taking end to end responsibility that is development to testing and delivery of product.

Supr Daily is a daily delivery service pioneering the grocery revolution in India. We leverage the power of the milk railroad to deliver eggs, bread, fruits, veggies, and other groceries to your doorstep by 7 am, daily.

N Sr Software Developer

Mordor Intelligence

May 2017 - Feb 2019 (1 year 10 months)

Mordor Intelligence is a market research and consulting firm with expertise in accurate research and analysis. 9,000+ comprehensive reports across 60+ industry segments. Trusted by 300+ brands across the globe.

Sr. Software Engineer

Celstream Technologies

Mar 2016 - Apr 2017 (1 year 2 months)

Designed the user interface Dash solution, it is basically designed for Airlines Media management. In this, have used Angularis, Angular Material, Asp.net WCF and Sql Server.

Airlines manage their Schedules according their plan, in which trip advertisement and Movie have to make accessible to the Traveler.

Junior Software Developer

Knowledgeflex Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

Sep 2014 - Mar 2016 (1 year 7 months)

I am Asp.Net Developer .Web Application developer and desktop application. I am working on Live project that is single handed ,Its realy challenging for me and fortunate to have this .



Webxperts

Mar 2014 - Aug 2014 (6 months)

I am software developer and worked on different different project and in different domain as well.

Education

📘 ShambhuNath Institute of engineering and Technology,Jhalwa Allahabad

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

2009 - 2013 cgpa - 7.3

Licenses & Certifications

Asp.Net with C# - CMC

Issued May 2013 - Expires Jul 2013

Honors & Awards

Stand Up Comedy Winner - Hero Honda

Jul 2012

In this i performed Stand Up Comedy and got prize for it.

I told people about some love stories which was comedy film.

Skills

HTML • JavaScript • AngularJS • React.js • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Leadership • Team Leadership • Web Design • Figma (Software) • Web 2.0